Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor (Elmer Ellsworth Brown) RG.3.0.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative Files
  - McLouth, Lawrence A. (Professor of German), 1911-1928 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - MacNeill, Hermon Atkins (Sculptor), 1932-1933 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - MacTavish, W. C. (Professor of Chemistry), 1928-1933 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Madden, John T. (Secretary, School of Commerce), 1917-1921 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Madden, John T. (Assistant Dean, School of Commerce), 1922 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Madden, John T., 1923 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Madden, John T., 1924 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Madden, John T., 1925 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Madden, John T. (Dean, School of Commerce), 1926 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Madden, John T., 1927 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Madden, John T., 1928 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Madden, John T., 1929 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Madden, John T., 1930 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Madden, John T., 1931 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Madden, John T., 1932-1933 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Madison Square Tower, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Magnes, Rabbi J. H., 1912, 1915, 1931 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Magoffin, Ralph Van Deman (Professor of Classics), 1923-1934 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Mandel, John A., 1917-1929 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Mannhardt, L. Alfred (Professor of Biology), 1922-1927 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Manning, William J., 1921-1931 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Marburg, Theodore, 1919-1932 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Marie Curie Radium Fund, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Marine Biology Station, Bermuda, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Markham, Edwin, 1927-1932 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Marks, Maurice, 1912 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Mason, Gabriel R., 1920, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Matthews, James M., 1925, 1931 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Medical Preparatory Course, 1912-1913 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Medicine, College of, 1912-1933 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Medley, 1933 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Meehan, John S. (Director of Physical Education), 1927, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Mellett, Don R., Memorial Lectureship, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Mendenhall, Harlan George, Ceremony, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Mendes, H. Pereira (Minister Emeritus, Spanish and Portuguese Congregation), 1919-1931 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Menorah Society, 1922-1933 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Mercer, Adelaide, 1924 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Mercier (Cardinal) Ceremony, 1919-1922 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Meredith, Albert B. (Connecticut State Board of Education), 1919-1932 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Merriam, John C. (President, Carnegie Institute), 1924-1933 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Mezes, Sidney E. (President, College of the City of New York), 1920, 1923, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Michigan, University of, 1918-1931 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1932-1933 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Mills, Harriette Melissa Training School for Kindergarten, 1917-1931 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Mindil, Clinton (Compiler of Records of Alumni and Students Who Served in the World War, 1920-1921 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Mitchell, Edwin Knox (Hartford Theological Seminary), 1919-1933 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Mitchell, John Purroy (Mayor, New York City), 1913-1917 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Monroe, James Memorial Association and Foundation, 1923 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Mooney, Edmund L., 1920-1934 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Morgan, J. Pierpont, 1922-1924 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Morris, Mr. And Mrs. Dave H., 1923-1931 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Morrison, Mr. And Mrs. B. Frank, 1920-1934 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Morrison, Woodman (Bureau of Public Information), 1922-1924 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B., 1912, 1929, 1932 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B.: Centenary of Birth, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B.: Commemoration, 1932 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Morton, Dr. Rosalie S. (Chairman, Serbian Education Committee), 1920-1928 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America, Inc., 1929-1933 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Mottet, Dr. Henry (Church of the Holy Community), 1920-1930 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Munn, James Buell (Chairman of the Executive Committee and Assistant Dean, Washington Square College), 1917, 1922-1928 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Munn, James Buell (Dean, Washington Square College; Advisor for The Arch, 1927-1932 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Munn-Recht, Aristine P., 1920-1921 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Museum of the City of New York, 1927 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Museum of Peaceful Arts, 1926-1930 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Music, Department of, 1923-1926 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Musser, John (Professor of History), 1926-1934 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Nadler, Marcus, 1929 1931 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Namm, Benjamin H. (President, A. I. Namm and Son Department Store), 1926-1932 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Nash, Jay B. (Professor of Physical Education), 1927-1931 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Nason, Arthur (Professor of English and Director, New York University Press), 1919-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Nathan, Alfred B., 1926 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Design, 1922 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - National Advisory Committee on Education, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1926-1927 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Master Plumbers, 1924-1925 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - National Civic Federation, 1919-1933 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1924-1933 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of Jews and Christians, 1928-1933 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1925-1930 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - National Economic League, 1923-1933 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - National Economy League, 1932-1933 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - National Education Association, 1919-1927 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - National Education Association, 1928-1933 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, 1927-1932 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - National Institute of Social Sciences, 1922-1926 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - National Kindergarten Association, 1920-1931 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - National Research Council, 1918-1933 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - National Security League, 1919-1921 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - National University of Mexico, 1928-1933 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - National University Extension Association, 1919-1920, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey State Chamber of Commerce, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - New Universal Encyclopedia, 1910, 1930-1933 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "New York" (Journal of Ideas for the General Reader), 1926-1930 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - New York American, 1918-1931 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - New York Campaign for Jewish War Sufferers, 1920, 1922 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - New York Evening Post, 1920-1932 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - New York Evening Sun, 1918-1933 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - New York Evening World, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - New York Globe, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - New York Herald, 1921-1923 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1925-1932 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - New York Music Week Association, Inc., 1923-1932 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - New York Peace Society, 1918-1932 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - New York State Board of Regents, 1930 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - New York State Wide Economic Congress, 1929-1933 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - New York Stock Exchange, 1925-1933 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - New York Sun, 1918, 1931-1932 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - New York Telegram, 1928 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - New York Times, 1913-1932 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - New York Tribune, 1918-1923 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - New York University: Charter and History, 1926-1927 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - New York University Daily News, 1921-1933 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - New York University Letter Club, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - New York University Press, 1912-1921 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - New York University Press, 1912-1928 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - New York University Press, 1929-1933 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - New York World, 1912-1931 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - New York World-Telegraph, 1931-1932 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Newark Evening News, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Newark Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1916-1917 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Newman, Allan T. (Dean of Dental School), 1930 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Newman Club, 1927-1934 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Nichols, William H. (Council), 1925-1929 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Nichols, William H.: Memorial Booklet, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Nixon, Albert B. (Graduate Manager of Athletics), 1922-1933 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Norton, Elliot S. (Chairman, Masaryk Anniversary Celebration Committee), 1928 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Ober, Frank W. (Secretary, Near East Relief), 1921-1925 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Ochs, Adolph S. (Publisher, New York Times), 1924-1933 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Office Personnel, Committee on, 1925-1927 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Offner, Richard (Professor of Fine Arts), 1924-1929 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Olyphant, Robert (Alexander Hamilton Institute), 1919-1927 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Onderdonk, Chester D. (Office Manager), 1925-1933 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Opolyke, John Baker (Chairman, Department of English), 1919, 1929-1930 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Oregon Memorial Trail Association, 1930-1931 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - O'Ryan, John F., 1919-1929 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield (President, American Museum of Natural History), 1920-1931 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Otiz, Arthur Hamilton (University of Arizona), 1923 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - The Outline of Christianity, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Owens, Georgiana H., 1922 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Owens, Robert L., 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Palmer, Bissell B., 1928-1929 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Pan American Union, 1920-1927 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Pan Hellenic Congress, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Pan Pacific Union, 1922-1923 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Paris, William Franklyn (Hall of Fame for American Artists), 1919-1925 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Paris, William Franklyn, 1926-1935 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Park, William H. (Dean, Medical School), 1914-1915, 1922-1934 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Pasteur Centennial, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Patterson, William M. (President, Law School Alumni Association), 1922, 1931-1933 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Paul, Francis H. J. (DeWitt Clinton High School), 1923-1927 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Payne, E. George (Assistant Dean, School of Education), 1923-1931 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Peabody, George Foster, 1923-1932 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Pettus, Isabella M. (Acting President, Woman's Legal Education Society, 1919-1931 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Phelps Lectures, 1920, 1928 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Phelps, William Lyon (Yale University), 1927-1933 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1920-1926, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1923-1933 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Phillips, John Preston, 1919-1930 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Pickett, Ralph (Secretary, School of Education Realty Corporation), 1924-1933 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Plant Personnel, Committee on, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Pollack Foundation fo r Economics Research, 1928-1929 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1924, 1930-1931 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Ponafidine, Emma, 1926-1928 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Porter, Chauncey R. (Assistant Secretary, School of Commerce, Accounts and Finance), 1918-1927 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Powell, Lyman Pierson (Professor of Government and Business Ethics), 1914-1926 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Poynton, John A., 1918-1930 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Pratt, Edward Ewing, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Preparation School Day, 1912 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Prohibition, 1926-1928 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Prokosch, Edward (Bryn Mawr College), 1927-1928 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Promotional Pamphlet, University and City, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Property, Supervisor of (Walter Cleverdon), 1919-1921 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Property, Supervisor of (Walter Cleverdon), 1922-1923 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Property, Supervisor of (Walter Cleverdon), 1924-1933 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Public Economy, Institute of, 1922-1923 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Public Health Service, Bureau of, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Public Information, Bureau of (Henry C. Hathaway), 1918-1924 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Public Information, Bureau of (Henry C. Hathaway), 1925-1926 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Public Information, Bureau of (Henry C. Hathaway), 1927-1930 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Public Information, Bureau of: Press Releases, 1920-1921, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Public Information, Bureau of: Press Releases, 1921-1922, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Public Occasions, Bureau of (Henry C. Hathaway, Director), 1920-1929 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Public Services of NYU Professors, 1926-1927 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1912-1918, 1931-1932 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Racca, Vittorio, 1914-1925 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Radio Broadcasting, 1925-1926 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Radosavljevich, Paul R. (Professor of Experimental Pedagogy), 1912-1933 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Rathbone, Henry B. (Professor of Journalism), 1925-1932 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Reed, Anna (Professor of Education; Managing Director, National Junior Personnel Service), 1924-1933 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Reed, Lewis Benedict, 1918, 1924 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Reed College, 1919 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Reeder, Rudolph R. (Marsh Foundation School), 1921-1934, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Reeve, Oscar C., 1922-1932, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Regional Plan of New York and Its Environs, 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Registration Statistics, 1920-1926 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Registration Statistics, 1927-1933 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Registration Statistics: Cumulative Data, 1907-1930 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Religious Activities at University Heights Campus, 1908-1911, 1932-1933 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Religious Education Association, 1913-1933 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1920-1932 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Report (Annual) of the Chancellor, 1922-1924 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Report (Annual) of the Chancellor, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Report (Annual) of the Chancellor, 1926 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Report (Annual) of the Chancellor, 1927, undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1915-1925 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1925-1926 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1926-1927 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1926-1927 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1927-1929 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1929-1930 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Reports of Deans and Officers, 1931-1932 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Registrar, 1919-1920 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1918-1919 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1918-1919 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1920-1925 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1926-1927 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1927-1928 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1929-1932 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Residence Bureau, 1922-1927 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Retail Dry Goods Association, 1918-1919 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Retail Selling, Training School for Teachers of, 1918-1921, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Retailing, School of, 1921-1932 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Rhodes Scholarship, 1912, 1924-1933 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Rice, Louis A. (Office Manager), 1924-1926 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Riddell, William Renwick (Justice, Supreme Court of Ontario), 1917-1929 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Riefstahl, Rudolph M. (Professor of Fine Arts, Roberts College, Constantinople), 1924-1932 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Rising, Lawrence A., 1920-1929 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Ritter, William Emerson, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Roberts, Vincent (Chairman, NYU Endowment Fund), 1919-1922 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Roberts, Vincent, 1923-1926, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Robertson, David A. (American Council on Education), 1927, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Robertson, Louis J., 1920, 1926 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Robinson, Frederick (President, City University of New York), 1925-1926, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, John Jr., 1919-1928 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1915-1930 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1919, 1928, 1933 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Roe, Joseph (Professor, Industrial Engineering), 1921-1926, 1930 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Rogers, Gustavus A., 1918-1932 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Rollins, Hyder (Pepysian Ballad Project), 1921-1926 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Romanoff, Prince, 1924 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Edith and Franklin, 1920-1933 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt (President Theodore) Memorial Association, 1919-1923, 1929 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr., 1918-1920, 1925 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Rosenfeld, Arthur N., 1926-1927 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Russell, Isaac Franklin (Professor of Law), 1911-1931 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Ryce, L. C., 1924-1925 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Sadler, Sir Michael (Sachs Memorial Lecture), 1923, 1930-1934 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Sage, Margaret (Mrs. Russell), 1912-1920, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Sailors Snug Harbor Trustees, 1913-1915 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Salvation Army, 1921-1933 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Sargent's Handbook Series, 1914-1916 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Scabbard and Blade, 1925-1931 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Schelling, Felix Emanuel, 1915 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Schepp, Leopold, 1926 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Schiff, Jacob H., 1912-1920 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L., 1915, 1920-1925 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships, 1913-1915 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships, Alumni, 1926 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships, Committee on, 1913 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships: Zona Gale, 1928 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Schreiber, Charles F., 1924-1925 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Schultze and Weaver (Architects, School of Education Building), 1925-1926 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould (President, University Club), 1920 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Schwab, Charles M., 1921-1922 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Scott, James Brown (Carnegie Endowment for International Peace), 1923-1926 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - SeBoyar, Gerald E. (Secretary, Beta Gamma Sigma), 1928-1934 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Semitics, Department of, 1921 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Senior, Harold D. (Professor of Anatomy, University and Bellevue Hospital Medical College), 1918-1931 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Service of New York University, 1920-1922 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Sesquicentennial Exposition, 1926-1927 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Shaw, Albert, 1913-1931 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Shaw, Charles (Professor of Philosophy), 1914-1932 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Sheldon, H. H. (Professor of Physics), 1922-1931 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Shelford, Rev. M. T. (Pastor, First Baptist Church, Hoboken, N.J.), 1920-1921 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Sherrill Lectures on American Relations, 1923 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Shields, Albert (U.S. Bureau of Education), 1912 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Shinn, Millicent, 1923, 1931-1933 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Short, Lois (Secretary, Student Activities at Washington Square Campus), 1923-1929 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Sihler, Ernest G. (Professor of Latin Language and Literature), 1912-1933 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Sihler, Henry J. (Commercial Photography), 1920-1921, 1925-1928 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Simon, Sir Ernest (University of Manchester), Informal Tea in Honor of, 1932 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Simon, Franklin, 1924-1931 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Simon, George A. (Superintendent and Treasurer, The Methodist Episcopal Church in the Baltic States, 1921-1931 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Simplified Spelling Board, 1913-1926 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Singer, Isidor (Literary Director, The Amos Society), 1921-1932 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Skinner and Cook Company (Elevator), 1931 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Smellage, Elizabeth, 1928 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Smiley, Effie (Mrs. Daniel), 1934-1935 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Smiley, Major Hugh, 1932-1933 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Governor Alfred E., 1923-1932 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Cornelius M. (Director, New York University Fund), 1919-1922 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Edgar F. (University of Pennsylvania), 1924-1930 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Edward C. (Professor of Political Science), 1922-1933, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Mrs. George Wilson, 1926-1927, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Ormond G. (College of Fine Arts): Instruction in Paris, 1928-1933 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Rufus D. (Assistant Dean, Washington Square College), 1915, 1920-1933 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Smith- Towner Bill (Federal Education Bill), 1918-1921 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1921, 1927-1932 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Smythe, J. Henry, Jr. (Executive Secretary, Benjamin Franklin Memorial Committee), 1927 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Snow, Charles H. (Dean, College of Engineering), 1914, 1918-1923 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Snow, Charles H. (Dean, College of Engineering), 1924-1926 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Snow, Charles H., 1927-1930 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Society for the Promotion of Engineering Education, 1923-1932 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Somerville, Randolf (Director of Dramatic Art), 1920-1931 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Sommer, Frank (Dean, School of Law), 1919-1932 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Sons of the Revolution in the State of New York, 1931-1932 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Southern California, University of, 1924, 1930-1933 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Southwestern Louisiana Institute, 1926 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Space Committee - University Heights, 1926 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Space Committee - Washington Square, 1925-1927 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Safford, Edward E. (National Commander, American Legion), 1927-1928 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Spanish, 1914, 1917 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Speyer, James, Esq., 1928-1933 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Sprague, C. Hayes (Professor of Advertising and Marketing), 1923-1932 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Sprague, Charles Ezra, Fund, 1922-1924, 1931 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Stable Money Association, 1926-1927 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Statutes of the University, 1912, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Stein, Elizabeth P., 1920-1928 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Stephens, Edwin Lewis (President, Southwestern Industrial Institute), 1921-1932, 1934 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Stevens Institute of Technology, 1921 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Stevenson, Archibald Ewing (Associate Council, State of New York), 1919-1921, 1928-1932 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Stevenson, John J. (Professor of Geology), 1912, 1918-1924 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Stewart, Dr. George D. (Chairman, Executive Committee, George Memorial Institute of Tropical and Preventive Medicine), 1919-1933 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Stewart, John A., Esq. (Chairman, The George Washington Bicentennial Commemoration Committee), 1922-1927 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Stitt, Dr. Edward W. (District Superintendent of Schools, NYC), 1920-1932 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Stockton, Mr. Lewis, 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Stoddard, 1919-1920 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Stoessel, Albert (Assistant Professor of Music), 1923-1931 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, Fund, 1911-1927 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, Fund, 1928-1933 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Stokes, James: Last Will and Testament, 1916 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Stokes Lectureship - Early American History, 1921-1926 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Stokes Lectureship - Politics, 1920-1931 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Stokes Lectureship - Chancellor Brown's Luncheon for Doctor Plooij, 1928 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Stout, Mr. Presley D. (Professor of Psychology), 1922-1933 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Straus, Nathan, 1915, 1922-1930 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Straus, Percy S. (President, Macy's), 1922, 1929-1935 (Box 67, Folder 6)